是的 先生
Yes, Sir.
对的 先生 这是必须的 先生
Correct, Sir. Absolutely, Sir.
您的床铺已经准备好了 先生
Your bed it's already made, Sir.
你们准备把家里变成旅馆吗?
Are you guys turning this place into a bed and breakfast?
我老爸要进城咯
Pops is coming into town.
哦! 太好了
Oh! Nice.
他仍然是世界上最骇人的老爸么? - 嗯哼
Is he still the most terrifying dad on the face of the planet? Mm-hmm.
伙计们 他一点都不吓人好吧
Guys, he's not that scary.
在你的婚礼上 他用剑指着我
He pulled a sword on me at your wedding.
好吧 首先 他穿了一套军装
Okay, first of all, he was in full military dress.
其次 你把我奶奶的淘气鬼(车名)开进了水塘
Second of all, you drove my grandma's rascal into a pool
-好吧 你奶奶和我一杯接一杯的喝
Okay, your grandma and I were going shot for shot,
-我就-- -嗯!你们知道那个杰里米吗?
And I was just-- ugh! You know that guy Jeremy
-我原来觉得很赞的那个? -嗯哼?
-That I thought was so a-mah-zing? -Mm-hmm.
他刚给我发鸡信 -鸡信?
He just pexted me. . "pext"?
用鸡鸡发短信-哦 哦
Penis text-Oh. Oh.
-喔 可真吃亏 -哇 也太小了吧
-wow. That's not worth it. -Whoa, that is small.
阿莱克斯和我现在是男人荒
Alex and I are in such a boy slump.
哇 等等 我才没有呢
Whoa, whoa. Back up. I am not in a slump.
我都没有想跟男人约会
I'm not even trying to date anyone.
女人荒是不会存在的
Girl slumps do not exist.
你们想知道怎么打破男人荒吗?
Do you want to know a foolproof way for a girl to break a slump?
第一步--准备上床 第二步--上床
Step one--decide to have sex. Step two--have some sex.
哦! 女人们开始行动咯
Oh! Women be shopping.
女人开始狩猎咯-没错
Women be shopping.-They do.
这个跟性交没关系好吧
It's not about intercourse.
关键是找个又拉风又体贴的人
It's about meeting someone who's cool and nice,
其中再穿插点性生活就完美了
And if intercourse happens to take place, no complaints.
也许你男人荒的原因
Maybe you're in a slump
就是你一直用"性交"这个词
'cause you keep using the word "intercourse."
想知道简怎么形容"性交"的吗?
want to know what Jane calls "intercourse"?
-别 -"坦诚相见"
-no. -Doing the "straight-up..."
哔!
beep!
啦 啦 啦 啦 "共浴爱河"
la, la, la, la. "...In sexy time valley."
-噢! -哦 哦 真的吗?
-Oh! -Oh. Oh, really?
要我帮你给他鸡信回去吗?
You want me to pext him back?
要鸡信就给brad（黑人的鸡鸡都很大）
If you're gonna do that, give it to Brad.
幸福终点站
第一季  第05集
==深影字幕组==
马科斯 别忘了买手纸
Max, just calling to make sure you remember the toilet paper,
和面包 还有我们快没番茄酱了
The bread, and we're almost out of ketchup.
这些鬼东西我都没买
I got none of that crap.
猜猜我买了什么好东西
but guess what I did get.
天哪，你没有
Oh, no, he didn't.
哦 是的 我有
Oh, yes, he did.
老兄 我们是不是早过了玩玩具的年纪?
Dude, aren't we a little old for toys?
盒子上写 "八岁以上适用" 我们玩正好
On the box, it says "ages 8 and up." that's us.
我干了一整天活 买了所有的生活用品
I work all day, I buy all the groceries,
还得做饭
I do all the cooking--
感激不尽 你真像我妈妈 但是更辣些
and I appreciate that. You're like my mom, but hotter.
算了吧 老兄 我指望你买草纸的
Come on, man, I am really counting on that toilet paper.
好吧 你怎么不用这个东东来善一下后?
Well, then why don't you clean your charlie sheen with this?
该我了
My turn.
怎么样? 怎么样 嗯哼!
What? What. Huh!
-没子弹了! -我也没了!
-I'm out of bullets! -I'm out of bullets, too!
-接下来怎么办?  - 我们叫马路上的
-What do we do?! -We call the homeless swede down the block
瑞典流浪汉要他给我们装子弹!
And tell him to be our ammo jockey!
我们也可以把那些从电视机上抠下来
We could just pi 'em up off the tv.
是啊 我才不想让他进我家大门
yeah, I don't want him going through my house.
你今晚准备和你爸爸干什么?
So what do you wanna do with your dad tonight?
他很早就会洗了睡的
He's gotta go to bed early.
-他明天早上要去医院做检查 -什么检查?
-He's going to the hospital for some tests tomorrow morning. -What kind of tests?
核磁共振 断层扫描 心电图
M.R.I., cat scan, e.K.G.
都是些常规检查 -常规?
Routine stuff. -Routine?
-哦 当然了 -不 那我所谓的常规是
-Oh, yeah, sure. -No, my morning routine is a cup of coffee,
早上一杯咖啡 乳房X光和阴道内镜检查
A mammogram, and a camera up my va-jane-a.
-你确定你爸没事吧? -肯定 如果有问题
-Are you sure everything is okay? -Totally. And if it wasn't,
-他早跟我说了 -是吗?
-I'm sure he would've talked to me about it. -Really?
我怎么觉得你们俩没太多共同语言?
'cause I kinda feel like you guys don't talk that much.
七点半 不
7:30. No.
斯科蒂 皮蓬
Scottie Pippen.
我是说不止是"公牛队何时比赛?"
I mean, more than just "what time is the bulls' game?"
"你去吗?" "如果让你选 "
"are you going?" and "if you had to sleep
"你想哪个公牛队员上床?"这样的话题
with one bull, who would it be?"
首先 他没这样问我
-okay, first of all, that's not what he asked me,
如果他问的话 我会选三分神射手阿姆斯壯
But if he did, the answer is B.J. Armstrong.
-那名字可不是白取的 -少胡扯
-You don't get that name for nothin'. -Clean it up.
B.J可以理解为口交的缩写
什么? 我说的是他的胳膊很粗壮
What? His arms are strong.
ARMSTRONY拆开为arm 和strong
Jane以为Brad说的是B.J
我的意思是 他可能会恐惧这些检查
-I'm just saying, he might be scared about these tests.
我觉得你真的该跟他好好谈谈
I think you should really talk to him about it.
好了 如果这样让你感觉好点
-Fine. If it'll make you feel better,
如果有合适的开场白 我会跟他谈的
I'll talk to him, if there's an opening.
太好了 别清了 房间已经很干净了
Great. And stop cleaning. The place looks great.
你怎么突然变身成我了?
Why you getting all "jane" on me?
你怎么总把你的名字加到每句话里面?
Why do you keep putting your name in every sentence?
-因为我就是Jane -别
-'cause that's how I jane. -No.
好了 我老爸总是很准时的
okay, my dad is always on time,
所以他应该到了
So he should be here
还有三 二 一
In approximately three, two, one.
哦
Oh.
不好意思 我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
嗨 弗朗西斯
Hi, Francis.
嗯...
Uh...
行李
Bags.
好了 我们要打破男人荒 我今晚感觉好极了
Okay, we are breaking the slump. I feel good about tonight!
打扰一下 美女们
excuse me, ladies.
这些排骨是那边那位先生送的
These ribs are from the gentleman across the bar.
我觉得不妙  这年代谁会送排骨啊?
And I feel less good. Who sends over ribs?
我们就当是喝酒游戏呗 好不?
We're turning this into a drinking game, okay?
我们要多跟帅哥搭讪
We'll talk to as many guys as we can.
如果第一感觉不好 我们就喝一杯
The first sign of creepiness, we take a shot.
耶! 姐喜欢 耶!
Yeah! I love it. Yeah!
到我家去休息下 怎么样 美女?
How about we retire to my apartment,
喝上一杯法国人所谓的长相思酒?
Where we can enjoy what the french call sauvignon blanc?
有种族歧视才性感
It's not sexist if it's racist.
然后我们可以做法国人所谓的3P
Then we can do what the french call le 3-way sex.
我一直在想 接下来会怎样 你们懂的..嗯
You know, I'm always thinking about what's next for me... mm.
-是啊 -我死后
-Sure. -In the afterlife.
嘣 嘣 宾邦!(拟声词)
Boom. Boom. Bing. bam!
莎拉 佩林--如果她是个黑人的话--
Sarah Palin--if she were black--
你们根本不知道自己是什么东西--算了吧
You guys don't know what you're--forget it.
-我看出来了你不愿意 -噗(拟声词)
-I'm getting a "no" from this side... -Pfft.
而你可能愿意?
And a "maybe"?
哇 这里压根儿没有酷哥
Wow. There are zero cool guys.
男人荒还在继续
Slump continues.
我不知道 我开始重新考虑排骨男了
I don't know. I'm kinda rethinking the rib guy.
你想做春梦么?
Do you need a wet-nap?
-我就是抱着这种心态吃的 - 我受不了了
-That's the way I eat 'em. -I can't watch this.
你慢慢来 ，别着急
You just gotta take it down, like a champ.
那么...
So...
布拉德 我们都到齐咯
Brad, here we all are.
现在是交流感受的最好时机了
Great time to ask people how people are feeling
那啥...发生的事
About things that are... Happening.
嗯
Mmm.
嗯 爸 我想问你你觉得那啥 嗯
Uh, yeah, dad, I wanted to ask you how you felt about, um,
公牛队新拍的九一年纪录片怎么样?
That new '91 bulls documentary.
我很喜欢啊
I very much enjoyed it.
重温过去的感觉很不错  那时候篮球
It's nice to go back to the days when basketball meant more
比起什么纹身啊
Than getting neck tattoos
在俱乐部当火枪手强多了
And shooting your pistol off in the club.
或者是传看卡戴珊的艳照什么的好多了
Or passing around a kardashian.
那是啥玩意?
What's that?
嗯 就是卡戴珊性爱光碟啊
Uh, there's these--these girls and a sex tape--
弗朗西斯...
so, francis...
医生明天要给你检查了?
Doctors are looking under the old hood tomorrow?
-你感觉如何? - 多少有点紧张 你懂的
-How you feeling about that? -Well, you know, you always worry a little bit.
-自然点 -我没事的
-It's only natural. -I'll be all right.
必须的
Totally.
好了 我要上床睡觉了 明天有得忙了
Well, I'm gonna turn in. Got a busy day tomorrow.
-简 -晚安
-Jane. -Good night.
布拉德
Bradley.
-见鬼 你怎么回事? -怎么了?
-What the hell was that? -What?
你没看到我给你"打开心扉"的手势了吗?
Didn't you see me make the "opening" gesture?
哦 是这个意思啊?
Oh, that's what that was?
我还以为你在试图扯开两只打架的老鼠
I thought you were separating two boxing mice.
你看成了啥?
That's what you thought this was?
哦 是啊 我也看到了 小白鼠
Oh, yeah. No, now I see it. Yeah. The little white one
-它叫什么来着?棕色的那个? - 泰森鼠
-what's that one's name? The brown one? -Mice tyson.
哦 泰森鼠! 太可爱了 我粉它们
Oh, mice tyson! So cute. I love them.
不管怎么样 他给你了个头
Anyway, he gave you an opening.
暗示的够明显了，你怎么不接着呢?
I mean, it was a clear shot. Why didn't you take it?
我爸和我好得很
-My dad and I are fine.
你跟你爸相互说过"我爱你"吗?
Have you and father ever even said "I love you" to each other?
没必要说出来
We don't have to say it
我们用行动证明爱
Because we show it by not saying it.
就像山从不向海言爱
Like how the mountains never say it to the sea,
-但是海知道 -说这句话之前你有没有好好
-And yet the sea knows? -All right, do you ever think about these things
想一下这个比喻说不说的通?
Before you say them or just--
怎么没想过 我想 "哇 我太有才了
yeah, I do. I think, "wow. That's brilliant.
我应该大声说出来" 接着 我就说了
I should say that out loud," and then I say it out loud,
效果很不错  简直超出我的预计
And it's spectacular. It exceeds my expectations.
算你狠
Right.
-我喝醉了 -今晚真衰 我们还是回去吧
I'm drunk. tonight was a bust. Let's go.
我有先见之明 录了个减肥节目
I dvr'd that new weight loss show for clairvoyants--
叫 "大手笔"
"large mediums."
哇 打住 姐们 来了两个帅哥
-whoa. Pump the brakes, sister. Two gorgeous guys,
来了
incoming.
你们好啊 好心的先生们
Hello, kind sirs.
你好两位辣妹，可惜俺俩不会说英语
当然了 他们俩只会说鸟语
Of course. They only speak gibberish.
我们终于等来了两个超帅的家伙
We finally meet two supercute guys,
结果他们只说意大利语
And they only speak italian.
真是够衰的
你会说意大利话？
我倒想，因为你俩实在贼帅
不幸的是，姐真的不会说意大利话
亲娘啊! 我居然说了这么多意大利语
Oh, my god! I speak a lot of italian!
听上去还是鸟语
Still gibberish.
你们可不会跟你老爸说"我爱你" 对不?
You guys don't say "I love you" to your dads, right?
-我总说 -我缺钱的时候说 所以时刻都在说
-All the time. -When I need money, so all the time.
简说我应该跟我老爸敞开心扉
'cause jane says I need to open up to my dad
多多交流 增进感情
About feelings and stuff.
如果我们真谈感情的话
If we're gonna have this emo conversation,
我会要你带上帽子的
I'm gonna need you to put on the hat. fine.
接招吧
There ya go.
哇 老兄 听着 你要真的为这事烦心的话
Aw, buddy, look, if it's really a concern for you,
就去跟他说你爱他 世事无常啊
Just tell him that you love him. I mean, life is uncertain.
你才说你爸爸住院了
One minute you're talking about your dad going into the hospital
要检查什么的
For some tests and stuff,
说不定下一分钟...就像现在这样儿了
And the next minute... This happens.
拜托 老兄
oh! Come on, guys!
别射我鸡鸡啊!
Not my sex nose!
检查结果一切正常
Tests came back fine.
谢天谢地
thank god.
你们真幸运摊上这么个健康的老爸
You're lucky to have such a healthy father.
真是太好了 谢谢你
That's great news. Thank you.
简 我仔细考虑了你说的话
You know, jane, I've been thinking about what you said,
我觉得这个机会不错
And I feel like this is the perfect opening
我去告诉他我爱他
For me to tell him I love him.
是啊 你必须这么做
Yeah. You gotta do it.
-我爱你 爸爸 -为啥跟我说这个?
-I love you, dad. -Why are you saying that to me?
你以前从来没说过 等等 什么意思
you never said that to me before. Wait. Why are you
你在胸口这么比划? 他们要给我开胸吗?
Doing this with your chest, man? Are they gonna cut me open?
我要死了吗? 不
Am--am I gonna die? No.
我要死了吗? 我不能死啊
am I gonna die? I-I can't die.
我还有很多事情没做啊
I got stuff I got to do.
医生 我真的要死了啊 我好害怕啊
am I-- am I gonna die, doc? I'm scared.
我对我爸爸说"我爱你"
So I said "I love you" to my dad,
差点要了他的老命 我再也
And it almost killed him. Never doing that
-不这么做了 -他就是吓坏了 没事的
-again. -He just had a panic attack. He's fine.
你们能互述"我爱你" 真是太赞了
It's good that you guys said "I love you" to each other.
是啊 真滑稽
Yeah. Funny story, though.
事实上 他从来没有对我说过我爱你 但是 没事
He never actually said it back to me. But, you know, it's okay.
他是我老爸嘛 他就是个很含蓄的家伙
He's my dad. He's a really reserved guy.
早上好 派对动物! 啊哈?
Good morning, party people! Huh?
我感觉棒极了 我第一次感觉自己活着
I feel amazing. I feel like I'm alive for the first time,
我有些话要说 布拉德...
And I got somethin' to say. Brad...
-什么? -我爱...
-Yeah? -I love...
这套运动服
This tracksuit.
真是太舒服了! 很宽松
Man, it is so comfortable! So much dangle room.
看看 看看 你能卖给我吗?
Look at that! Hey, look, can I buy this from you?
爸 我的就是你的
Dad, you can have it.
-你愿意吗? -当然啦
-You'd do that for me? -Of course.
布拉德
Brad.
我爱...
I love...
爱死这套运动服了
This tracksuit so much.
上身感觉太好了 你知道我想做什么吗?
It just feels so good. You know what I want to do?
-抢银行还是? -我想再活五百年!
-Some racketeering or-- -I want to live!
好了 来吧 让我们跳起来
Okay. Come on. Let's go get jiggy with stuff.
现在 我要上楼去 扔掉
Now I'm-a go upstairs and throw away
所有不运动的衣服 因为我以后就穿这个了
All my non-track-style suits because this is my new look.
让我们跳起来 哦哦~ 我跳起来了
We gon' go get crunk. Ooh! I'm getting crunk!
哦 哦 好吧 这些都是怪异的举动
Oh. Oh, okay. Those are weird moves.
嗯 看看这个 呼 呼 明白了吗 他放开了
Mm? Look at this! Hoo-hoo! see? He's... Opening up.
是的 对于 嗯 运动服和90年代的行为
Yeah, to, uh, tracksuits and '90s slang.
噢 宿醉好难受
oh, I am so hungover.
我也是，肚子还很奇怪的非常饱
Me, too. And I'm, like, weirdly full.
你昨晚把酒吧一半的排骨都吃光了
You ate a half slab of ribs last night,
然后又要了一整块
Then chased it with a full slab.
你打败了那个一口流利说意大利语的人
You busted out fluent italian.
的确是那样 是吧?
I did, didn't I?
我跟他说，你想让老娘和那只鸡一起洗泡泡浴？
你当这里海天盛筵啊
你确实在佛罗伦萨呆过一学期
I mean, you did spend that semester in florence.
或许你确实被那些意大利人同化了
I mean, maybe some of that italian actually sunk in.
啊 那些甜美醉倒的意大利红酒之夜
Ah, those sweet chianti-soaked nights,
在阿诺河边的银行散步
Strolling the banks of the arno,
遇见来自全国各地叹为观止的人物
Meeting amazing people from all over the big ten.
好吧 别炫耀了 - 如果我昨晚能说
All right, stop bragging. If I could speak it last night,
为什么这些我都听不明白呢?
Why don't I understand any of this?
我是说 听上去就像谜语
I mean, it's, like, a mystery.
汉语 但实际上那是意大利语
Chinese, but it's actually italian.
好吧 我是说 今天和昨晚有什么不同的地方呢
Yeah. I mean, what's different from last night?
我不清楚 但我要弄明白
I don't know, but I gotta figure it out,
因为我真的喜欢这个人
'cause I really like this guy.
说了N遍了亲
I feel like you say that a lot.
我是说 有什么不一样吗? 还是一样的我啊
I mean, what's changed? I'm still the same old me.
我只是没有喝醉而已
I'm just not hammered.
对 就是这样 能给我们来杯鸡尾酒吗
Yep. That's it. Can we get a round of mimosas, please?
哦 来吧 好的 这听起来很酷
Oh, come on. Okay, that sounds cool.
#嗨 来跳曼波舞 曼波舞 意大利诺#
hey, mambo, mambo italiano
#嗨 嗨 来跳曼波舞# 嗯
hey, hey, mambo mmm!
#曼波舞 意大利诺 走吧 走吧 走吧
mambo italiano, go, go, go,
你混合的西西里舞蹈# 嗯 好吧
you mixed-up siciliano
嗯! 好吧
Mmm! Okay.
ciao就是你好的意思
"ciao" is "hello."
pennissima就是小彭妮的意思
"pennissima" is "little penny."
就听明白这两句 继续喝
That's all I got. Drink.
#跳伦巴舞#
dance the rumba
服务好贴心 是啊 我喜欢她
Good service. Yes. I love her.
她在那 如此可爱 她那么甜美 她如此漂亮
She's on it. So cute. She's so sweet. She's so pretty.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嗯
Eh.
夫人!
Ma'am!
她是个婊子
she's a bitch.
#当你跳起意大利的曼波舞#
when you mambo italiano?
你好 彭妮
"hello, penny.
"今晚请在同时一时间同一地点来见我们
"please meet us at the same time and place tonight.
带你的朋友"
Bring your friend."
噢 天呐 一喝醉我就会说意大利语了
Oh, my god. When I get drunk, I speak italian.
噢 天呐 一喝醉我就狂吃排骨了
oh, my god. When I get drunk I eat ribs.
那么你昨晚玩的开心吗?
So did you have fun last night?
是的 可以这么说
Yeah, sorta.
嗨 现在让我们来聊下女人吧
Hey, now let's talk to some women,
你知道 和她们做爱吧
You know, "try and have sex with 'em."
好吧 哥不好那口 不过你们说
okay. Not my thing, but okay.
爸爸 嗯 拜托别说了
Dad, uh, please stop.
伙计 自从有了你妈妈 我就时时饥渴
'cause ever since your mom lt, man, I'm super horny.
我是说 超级难以自制
I mean, it makes it hard to drive.
噢 妈呀
Oh, god.
你知道 当他从来没说他爱什么的时候还好
You know, it was fine when he never said he loved anything,
但是昨晚 他把爱心炸弹炸得到处都是
But last night, he was dropping "l"-bombs all over the place.
但是没有一颗击中我
Not one of 'em hit me.
布拉德 我真的爱...
Brad, I really love...
你的朋友们  - 耶
Your friends. yeah.
我的新爸爸 逊毙了
My new dad. Stings a bit.
亲爱的我知道 但我打赌如果再跟他说一次
I know, honey, but I bet if you say it to him again,
他会跟你说的 你只需营造一个
He'll say it right back. You just need to create
合适的氛围  你知道吗?
The right moment. You know what?
你应该腾出一天不工作时间
You should take the day off work
跟他来个父子约会
And you should take him on a dad date.
好吧 但我不会这样称呼
Okay, but I'm not calling it that.
父子约会听上去像一个恐怖的迈克尔 基顿
"dad date" sounds like a terrible michael
的电影 - 或者一部超棒的泰德 丹森电影
keaton movie. Or an amazing ted danson movie.
#我的孩子就在几天前降临了#
my child arrived just the other day
#他按通常的方式来到这个世界#
he came to the world in the usual way
#但是我必须要赶飞机和支付账单#
but there were planes to catch and bills to pay
#当我不在的时候他学会了走路#
he learned to walk while I was away
别扔它 别仍
Don't throw it. Don't throw--
嗨! 你们他爹的搞什么?!
Hey! What the hell are you doing?!
嗨! 过来! 回来!
Hey! Come here! Come back here!
#猫的摇篮时代和银色的勺子#
and the cat's in the cradle and the silver spoon
#月亮中的人跟蓝色的小男孩#
little boy blue and the man in the moon
#儿子当你回家时#
"when you coming home, son?"
该死! 该死!
Damn! Damn!
#但等会我们又会聚在一起 爸爸# 嗨 嗨
"but we'll get together then, dad" hey! Hey!
#我们渡过了很好的时光#
"we're gonna have a good time then"
回来!
Come back here!
伙计 这是最美好的一天
man, that was the best day ever.
我喜欢这一切
I loved everything about it.
有什么特别的事或者人是你今天喜爱的吗
Anything or anyone in particular that you loved today?
没有 到最后 我喜欢这一天
Nope. Tip to tail, I loved the day.
先生们 你们点的菜 - 噢 不 看看这个
Here you go, gentlemen. Oh, no, look at this.
他给我们上了龙虾泥跟奶油菠菜
He brought us the lobster mash and the creamed spinach.
这家伙 来这里 抱一下抱一下
This guy--come here. Bring it in. Bring it in.
真的? - 什么?
Really?  What?
你在抱一个服务生 布拉德
You're hugging waiters now? Brad.
瞧 爸爸 我喜欢新的你 但困扰我的是
Look, dad, I love the new fran, but it kinda bothers me that
新的你喜欢一切和所有人  除了我
The new fran loves everything and everyone except me.
对我来说  说"我爱你"是超级困难
It was super tough for me to say "I love you,"
但你却没有任何回应  -我要为
And you didn't even say it back. In my
自己辩驳一下  我以为我是心脏病发作
defense, I thought I was having a heart attack.
而且你知道我对你的感觉 我的意思
Besides, you know how I feel about you. I mean, what says
说"我爱你"能比多放几次鞭炮更有意思？
"I love you" more th setting off firecrackers?
说"我爱你"?
Saying "I love you"?
好吧 好吧 让我再试一次
Okay, fine. Let's try it again.
好吧
Fine.
爸爸 我爱你
D, I love you.
爸爸
Dad?
爸爸 爸爸 我 这很好 我太情绪化了
Daddy? Dad, I--it's okay. I'm emotional, too.
哇 我想我从未见过你哭过
Wow. I don't think I've ever seen you cry before.
这是一个巨大的突破 我知道你喜欢这个牛排
This is a huge breakthrough. I know you like the steak.
这就是我为什么带你到这来-嗯
That's why I brought you here. Mm!
这是块好牛排-噢 天呐先生
It's good steak. Oh, my god! Sir?
哇
whoa!
你还好吧 感谢上帝
You're okay. Thank god.
你救了我 不 不 不 别动
You saved my life. No, no, no. Don't move.
快用这对宽阔强壮的双臂抱抱我
Those big, strong arms-- bring it in.
抱一个 - 嗨 该死的 抱你自己的老爸去
Bring it in. Hey, get your own damn daddy.
嗯 佩妮又跟那个意大利人出去了
Mm. Penny's out with the italians again.
他们不想和你一起吗? -我不认为他们喜欢我
They didn't want you to go with them? I don't think they like me.
啊 我是马里奥 我会赢一个
eh, I'm mario. I'm-a gonna win-a.
啦 啦 啦 啦
La, la, la, la.
随便啦 为什么我会想在那里
Whatever. Why would I want to be there anyway
反正我什么都听不明白  - 你说了同样的话
If I can't understand anything? You said the same thing
当你八年级想要辍学的时候
When you tried to drop out of eighth grade.
伙计们 我们能专注一些重要的事吗
Guys, can we focus on what's important,
那就是我找不到酷的目标来射击了
Which is that I've run out of cool things to shoot?
16 17 18 19
16, 17, 18, 19...
不 不 年轻人
No! No teen!
$20.
我起不来了 - 你可以的
I can't get myself up. You can do it.
戴夫 我做不到 - 要掉下来了!
Dave, I-I can't do it. Going down!
好吧 你们这把年纪是不是不适合再玩玩具了?
Okay, aren't you guys a little old to be playing with toys?
不是吧?
Honestly?
噢 你在跟我开玩笑吗
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me.
对面有个日本石国
There's a total chach across the street
在嗅一个性感女孩的鞋
Sniffing a hot girl's shoe.
这是维生素商店的阿维
That's avi from the vitamin store.
看到蜡烛跟迷你和服了吗
Notice the candles and the mini kimono.
是的 他很注意细节
Yep, he thinks of everything.
先生们 我们有下一个目标了
Gentlemen, we have our next target.
嗨
Hi.
嗯
Mm.
早上我做个梦
但是个出了一身汗的噩梦
嗯 嗯 嗯 嗯 嗯 嗯 嗯
Mm. Mm. Mm. Mm. Mm. Mm.
佩妮
Penny...
你是我悲惨世界里的一道亮光
嗯
Mm.
我爹是个恶心的酒鬼，他喜欢用皮带抽我
笑死我了
Stop it!
噢 噢 伙计
Oh! Oh, man!
终于有一天，他的皮带断了，但第二天，他又买了条新皮带
是条业余拳击手的冠军皮带，那天晚上他用那条皮带把我打的死去活来。
嗯 棒
Mm. Mm-hmm.
佩妮
Penny...
你为什么要嘲笑我的伤心往事
失陪下
哎呀
Whew.
噢 噢
Oh! Oh!
我不敢相信我们在射击那个穿迷你和服的男人
I can't believe we've been shooting at mini-kimono guy
一个半小时过去了我们还没有打到他
For an hour and a half and we still haven't hit him.
补充说明 我不能相信
Sidebar--I can't believe
他一直做了一个半小时的爱
He's been having sex for an hour and a half.
关窗户了  他关他的窗户了
The window is closing. He's closing his window.
我们的射击靶跑了 - 好吧 我想是的
We're missing our shot. Well, I guess that's it.
那就只剩一件事情要做了 - 打扫房间?
There's only one thing left to do. Clean the house?
看 大媒体 - 不 另一件事
Watch "large mediums"? No. Another thing.
我喜欢这伙计
God, I love that guy.
他会被抓的-不会
He's gonna get caught. No way.
我们的小家伙MAX超级会潜行的
My boy max is super stealthy.
拉下窗户
Pull down the window.
Pull it down.
现在是时候上了
Now it's go time.
是 好的 戴夫 就这个点
Yes! All right, dave, this this it.
子弹拿好
Take the shot.
哎呀
Whew.
哼
Huh?
这下我们真的要坐牢了
And we're going to prison.
啊
Ahh.
这个点就喝酒不有点太早了吗
尤其是俺刚告诉你我爹以前喝醉酒怎么打我的
你说啥
你没听我说话吗
他残忍的打我，直到他被一个他无法战胜的拳击手打败
他得了肝硬化
噢 天呐!
Oh, my god!
PENNY 别让喝酒毁了你的生活
但我喝酒是为了你，为了我们两个
你是在用我爹喝醉酒打我的时候说的话来嘲笑我吗
PEENY 再会
别走，我真的喜欢你，你是我唯一遇到的正常的男人
这是个严重的失误
This was an incredible trip--
参观千禧公园 购了一些物
Saw millennium park, did a little shopping,
差点死了两次 - 是的
Almost died twice. Yep.
你知道 这次的经验让我意识到
You know, this experience made me realize
这使得我需要活的轻松一点
That I need to live a little.
你做得对 - 也许不必完全这样
You sure do. Maybe not quite this much.
绝对是  - 嗯 嗯
Absolutely. Mnh-mnh.
这使得我意识到
It also made me realize
我应该向我的儿子说"我爱你"
I need to say "I love you" to my son.
啊 爸爸 啊
Aw, dad. Aw!
哪里
Shucks.
我让你们俩待会
I'm gonna leave you two.
这足以让她安心一阵了
That should hold her for a while.
好 是的
Good. Yeah.
你知道 我真的很爱你
You know, I really do love you.
只是我并不擅长表达  - 这很好
Just saying it isn't my thing. That's cool.
我擅长的是运动服
My thing is gonna be tracksuits
轻柔地去到脱衣夜总会
And light to moderate strip-clubbing.
没那么酷了
Less cool.
抱一个 抱一个
bring it in. Bring it in.
噢
Ohh.
噢 天呐 噢 天呐 噢 上帝! 这太糟了
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god. oh! This is bad.
好吧 噢 不 这是克莱恩夫人!
Okay. Oh, no, that's mrs. Klein!
噢 天呐 克莱恩夫人受伤了么?
Oh, my god. Did mrs. Klein get hurt?
哦 没有 这场火灾中没人受伤
Oh, no. No one was hurt in the fire.
六天前 她跌倒了 摔粹了盆骨
She fell and shattered her pelvis six days ago.
事实上 如果不是这次火灾
In fact, if it wasn't for the fire,
她可能会被饿死
The poor thing would've starved to death. Whew!
哇 得到了一个教训
Wow. Gotta be a lesson here.
是 你是对的 我们已经过了玩玩具的年纪了
Yeah, you were right. We're too old to be playing with toys.
不 伙计 我们这回算是英雄
No, man. We're kinda heroes here.
我的迷你和服!
My mini kimono!
它被毁了! 它被毁了!
It's ruined! It's ruined!
看  我们是超级英雄 三击掌
Check that. We're superheroes. Tri-five.
嗨 进展怎样?  马科斯 嗨 好吧
Hey, how's it going? Max. Hey. All right.
你们做得很好 做了老天爷的工作
You guys doing good work, doing the lord's work.
完事后有没有人要喝酒啊 罗萨塔的
Anybody wanna get a drink after? Rosalita's.
嗨 那个水龙带看上去很重
Hey. That hose looks heavy.
噢 医生来了
Ooh, the doctor is in.
我只是沏了一些石榴黑茶
I just brewed up a batch of some pomegranate kombucha.
噢 不要介意我做
Oh. Don't mind if I do.
你知道 我很高兴我们在维他命商店见面
You know, I'm so glad that we met at the vitamin store.
嗯 告诉我你最喜欢的补充剂是什么?
Mm. Tell me--what's your favorite supplement?
嗯 好吧 如果我只能选择其一 噢
Mm. Well, if I had to pick just one... Oh, yeah?
我想选 维他命D（双关DICK，鸡鸡）
I'd say... vitamin d.
嗯 不错的选择
Mm. good choice.
但是如果我还要在清单上再加一个
But if I had to pick another one on the list,
我肯定会选维他命 性爱
I'd definitely say vitamin... Sex.
噢 我每天都补充 噢 是的
Ooh, I take that one daily. Ooh. Yes.
让我赶紧准备下  - 快点回来
Let's crank up some enya. Hurry back.
见鬼去吧 阿维
See you in hell, avi.
哦 哦 噢 啊
oh! Oh! Oh! Ah!
噢 噢 呼 是
Oh, ho, ho! Yeah!
正中部位!
Right in the sex nose!